Asa-chan is Asa-chan. , we are upctre oneshota!
I couldn't get it together.
What is it?
I've been called out. What is this?
Today, we will show the results of our training.
We're going to do the Nukkushi dance!
What?
The five of us, ladies and gentlemen.
Musha Shugyo Free Live!
We went to 5 places in Japan, right?
Yes, we did.
We'll be able to dance one song even if we have to do a wet comb
You can dance, right?
I don't remember.
What song?
The song you will dance to today is...
"Mushroom University Industry Theme.
Oh!
That's the one you did just one year ago.
You're kidding.
I can't move.
I was going to go with the lemon one we did last time.
How's everyone doing with their own holoho-colors?
Holoho-coated.
Five of us bumped into each other.
We're trying to build trust.
I'm going to do my best.
Mushroom University Industry Theme
How are you guys doing?
I feel like we're going to bump into each other.
But I'm going to do my best.
It's a school year.
Yeah, right.
Oh!
Yes, I win things!
Ehhhh...
Let's do this.
I'm gonna be mad now.
That's funny.
I'm really scared.
Scary.
Oh, man.
I'm impressed that you're doing this.
Wait a minute.
Be careful not to freak out.
Yes, sir.
Oh, I'm scared.
How about this?
How about the first pose?
Yes, you can take the first pose.
Okay, here we go.
I'll do the first pose.
Okay. - Okay.
Oh, I'm scared.
Here we go.
Next time preview
Next trailer
Next preview.
From all of us at cũng 춤 Ofunatoryo
Introducing the success of the first dayIntroducing First Day Success
I've grabbed your hand and I've done it
Manihov do shirinuru bo machiyotare choture run run run run
Beyond orhythms and mottos, let's have a hot dream, Eamonsei
(Reincarnate, go to hell, reef, even if you say I'm shy, it's no joke)
Uniforms are kinda tight
Baaaaaaaa compose by andreo
Baaaaaaaa compose by projeet
Me.
Give me a break, I don't want to be introduced to you.
Give me a break, I want to misunderstand, I want to get lost
more than you can imagine more than you can imagine
it's the first time I'm getting a cup, so no
I want to stay!
I love you forever
Pink Panty Girl
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
I Want To Love You Extreme
Everyday Everyday
Everytime Everywhere
Love so fine
It's time to die
Pink Panty Girl
Love so fine
Ending
I'm so happy
You're so happy, aren't you?
I can't help it, I'm so happy
I'm happiest when I'm with you.
Hey, it's like this. It's gonna be like this forever. We're in middle school.
All right?
Hey, I'm happiest when I'm with you.
Happy class, everybody!
Better tonight.
Better than ever!
better than ever
ever ending earth
EVER ENDING Earth
🐼
😂
Can I take off my blindfold?
Please take off the blindfold!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I don't have any more.
Oh, that's so cool!
Okay, now that I'm done.
Let's have a look.
Let's see how it's done.
This way.
Oh, it's beautiful at first.
Beautiful at first
Ahhh...
Great, the cheaters were so loud.
I couldn't hear a thing.
Oh, it's working.
I can do it.
I can do it.Oh, I can do it.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Let's look at it for a while.
I can do it, I can do it.
That's it.
Where did I just go?
I just dropped out.
Boom, boom, boom.
LOL!
LOL
LOL!!!
Now that was a full bath.
It was a full bath now.
It was a full bath now
Thank you for your hard work.
I already have a little sore throat.
My throat's a little sore.
You want a left?
Oh, yeah, sure.
That's good.
That was another one.
It's okay.
Ow, ow, ow.
Oh, God, why?
This is it.
After all.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, you're singing just by saying it
He's singing.
Oh, that's funny.
I wish it was an image like this.
Eh, but always
If you do it all the time, Domi's a bit...
Your face is funny.
Ah!
I feel like Yuna's in here.
I bent my leg.
Yuna!
Yuna, where are you?
Yuna, come here.
I'm in trouble.
Yuna!
I was just flushing.
-orman.
No.suffix used to negate a verb in the non-past tense
more than enough
There was
-Thanks.
-There was...
-Oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
It's too hard!
Oh, no.
Oh no!
I'm going to get closer.
I've never seen anything like this.
Aren't you scared again?
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
It's coming.
I like the first one at the end.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
The first part at the end is good.
Makinus
Good bye again.
Yes, ma'am.
Emma, you were terrible.
Emma, you were amazing from the start.
No, it wasn't.
I don't know.
It was pitch black.
Did everyone speak English?
They were speaking English.
You want me to change?
I'm next.
Second year.
Oh...
Let's see...
Fourteen years old.
Oh, that's not fair.
Senior members don't have long experience.
Oh, I see.
I'd be curious to know what he was like.
Or ten.
I want this guy.
Only the senior member.
This one.
I want you to do it.
Which one of you can do it right?
Oh, yeah!
That was so much fun.
It was so much fun!
YouTube.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Subscribe to our channel
Please click the "Good" button!
Bye bye!